Is this going to happen?
Ah, I've got a boat!!
You're typing the piss.
Do it, seated, basted!
You know, don't polish in that
thing,
yeah?
You know, don't be in a
miserable sweat.
Boy, that is what you joy.
You're not on this end home.
But I get it.
Let's take a look.
Let's go.
It's missing one thing
though.
Boy, room.
Sorry,
sir.
Chaps?
Station commander Richardson is joining us
today.
Morning, nine sections.
Good morning, sir.
Sir.
What's your name?
Excuse me,
sir.
Good morning, sir.
That's so cute.
Something to do with the best.
Physician's voice.
Sir, sir.
Start, sir.
Good morning, sir.
Sir, Michael, the act is all
defend the SIG battler.
The act protection against the wickedness
is theirs in the devil.
I mean, got him.
I mean, I've got him to
be a human, we only pray.
And do thou, Prince of the
Meele'sd, and by the power of
God, the casting, the hell's sating?
And all these spirits who drown
about the hour.
Ah!
Seeking the Renaissance.
All right.
Tony, stop it!
You sit.
Come on, honey.
Come on.
Hey, boy, excuse me.
The Dutchen.
There's a train store of three
o 'clock.
Let's see if we can make
a nuisance about ourselves.
Bring it home tonight.
Got us, be ready!
Come on.
Come on, honey.
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Come on,
honey.
Come on.
Come on, honey.
Come on,
honey.
Come on.
Come on, honey.
Come on,
honey.
Come on, honey.
Come on,
honey.
Come on, honey.
Let's make this quick.
Come on!
Come here.
Ah!
Target!
Five!
Hold on!
Another!
Reline!
Two!
Anywhere!
Three! Time!
Ah!
A concrete shot!
Sergeant, on my mark! Stop!
What's going to do?
Stop!
I've got it! I've got it!
No!
Rice!
Target!
Five!
Hold on!
Ah!
Yes!
Shut up! Don't get caught!
Stop!
Stop! Don't yet!
Move on! Stop!
Stop! Stop!
No!
Gas! Gas!
Stop! No!
Providence! Just smoke!
Jerry tries to blind us!
No!
Go!
Stop!
No, no!
No!
Oh, oh, oh...
All right.
It's like a bloody mess, but
you'll be all right.
Everyone, all right.
Fuck.
...
You know what I mean?
You're right,
right,
right, yet, right, yet.
Let's see.
Let's see if we can't get
ourselves out of here.
Someday!
I'm going to get you out
of my way.
What are you doing here?
No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no,
no,
no...
Robert Brady,
sir?
I'm ditching you,
yes sir,
I'm going ahead and you too.
I'll go.
Leave him a chance sir.
Boy, you guys not.
I'm going ahead and you too.
Go ahead and you too.
Why is it?
Get back inside.
Boss, get back inside!
I'm going ahead and
you too.
I'm
going
ahead and you too.
I'm
going
ahead and you too.
I'm going ahead and you too.
I'm going ahead
and
you too.
You got it in the throat.
I don't get it.
Did you see where it came
from?
I'm shocking, I don't know where.
So one of them though.
What do you have to go
so?
You have to come beside behind
you.
Right,
sir.
Nothing doing private.
I'll boys will be here soon.
I'm going ahead and you too.
I'll just go ahead and you
too.
It's easy,
mate.
Yeah.
оч...for
us.
This
agreement was with shell rats.
Was
it greater than you? I
will not need today's shell accurately!
How
much?
These
rice! We
to be good enough.
Mei.
Na.
Meins rugs bow.
Welsons.
Oh, hey, hey.
He'll be so much the strongest,
he'll be the only one who's
here.
All right, let's go for now.
We're going to wait for him
for treat to get it.
Do you know what I mean?
But you just aren't going to
end up getting us okay with
no one in the heavens?
You said that, I've tell you
what I was thinking of, when
I was going to get it.
You didn't so much as bad,
and all right.
If you were ever left in
the new hour, I'd be able
to simply let him know.
Good to see you all back
with us, bud.
It's just a poster.
Wanted to head me and not
some sandstone,
son?
Let's start with that.
It's what?
Right up in the.
So,
I need you to do an
ammunition camp.
We only just need one, sir.
That may be you,
but...
I don't know how to make
work for the level, probably.
When you agree.
Yes, sir.
Sorry, sir.
Good morning.
Carry on.
Do you think the infantry will
start to move up?
Your guess is as good as
mine.
Let's keep another shot, if you
can't pull yourself up.
Sergeant?
I don't know what.
Ready?
Butt!
I'm steady, my steady.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Are we doing private?
That nice,
sir.
I can't see straight.
There'll be something.
Butt.
You and me.
We're gonna get through it, is
it?
No way.
We're supposed to be too bloody,
buddy.
Send this to the carry for
you.
Private, then we get on the
floor with the rest.
Now.
Take him up for my munition.
Are you deaf, man? Get a
bloody move on.
Listen up, listen well.
I don't like this anymore than
the rest of you, but we
have a job to do, so
I'm not going under.
Oh, my Christ, I will bring
the hammer down.
The lock is my shepherd, I
shall not walk.
Make it mean to lie down
in green pastures.
I need to be on the
side, this is the wall, this
is the wall.
Get this door at my shoulder.
Careful not to break it,
tooth.
Joel will like it.
Yeah.
You're bleeding all that.
No, I'll feel no evil.
We'll show good.
I prefer to keep my faith
in a fully loaded list for
the shop where I rise behind.
This gets fighting this way,
yeah.
Do you want that for me?
Do you reckon Jerry's going off
to bed?
Listen.
Can be boost.
What are
you
doing?
I'm ditching baby.
You're a boy of mine, so
what are you?
Keep your eye skin.
If you see anything,
don't hesitate.
Ready?
Let's go.
You're right?
I'm fine.
Let's go.
Let's come in from our lines.
Use this bloody pigeon.
What do we go, Charlie?
What are you looking at?
Rockin' out there.
Jerry.
All clear, one second, and then.
Very lost.
Move it there!
They're playing games.
Making your voice starting to be
an issue chasing the fat dumps.
Why?
The frighteners off.
They're on the prize, but on
the fight.
First jump in units, come to
a British tank for the Kaiser,
even ordered us heroes.
I am crosses all around.
But my motivation couldn't hit it.
I don't want to have a
shot to get me back, sir.
Don't do all the fire.
I'll never make it.
If it doesn't dream in the
mud, they'll be shot in one
of the pieces within minutes.
If somebody doesn't try, they'll all
be brought into pieces.
Besides, I don't recall asking for
your opinion.
Private.
This is an insane machine.
God or shall I know it
away?
I have to stay aside.
God fucked off years ago.
Your age has been in the
hands of 12th week, Pepson,
and I'll have you on a
charge.
Do it! I make myself clear.
I don't
know
what to do.
So, Michael, the Archangel, they've found
us in battle.
The intersection against the wickedness
and
the devil.
We have to make God review,
can we hardly pray.
And do thou, or Prince of
Emily, host?
And by the power of God,
the cast into hell, Satan,
all the evil spirits who prowl
about the world.
Sicken the rumors, souls.
Problem.
Cloth.
I'll fill my mouth.
And I'll fill my mouth.
Please, please, please.
Come on!
Ah, ah, ah, ah...
Come on, come on!
Sorry, Fondou...
Ah! Ah, ah!
In the newspapers house.
Finley.
Pasta won't front.
两个人?
三个人?
六个人?
两个人?
五个人?
三个人?
So
Tonight
Get ready
Keep going
Say the bastard
They might get him up for
it
They say
This is what happens when we
take our eye off the ball
Now we're at the blast of
infantry
Now
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go!
Go,
go, go!
We can do everything that we
can do.
What are you suggesting?
Anything!
Anything may be better than sat
here!
Wait for something to happen!
That's the nature of soldiering private.
Can I see? Just last in
an idea?
I want to have a question.
When the infantry arrived, they'll bring
up a bus to pull us
out.
If our boys will come in
the video, by now.
Yes, I get you seem to
have forgotten your place!
Private!
I see you!
Last!
Let's see.
We can still be at your
side.
Not really the private, but...
No!
You know, a tank isn't much
use of that screw.
You know,
a tank isn't much use of
that, but you know, a tank
isn't much use of that screw.
That's a good idea.
What
are
you saying?
What do I say?
F
Yes, I remember.
Say, we'll call this label out
then,
yeah?
They'd start drifting away.
He was announced, he just
showed the hoax as far.
We're split a few, kind words,
and then it clear.
We'll just roll it into Adam
Packer.
You guys?
That's always the truth.
Shearing seems to have finally stopped,
sir.
Maybe Misson did make
it.
I wouldn't go to bed.
Get out of
here!
We'll just roll it into Adam
Packer.
We'll
just
roll it into Adam Packer.
We'll just roll it into Adam
Packer.
We'll
just
roll it into Adam Packer.
We'll just roll it into Adam
Packer.
We'll just roll
it into Adam Packer.
We'll
just
roll it into Adam Packer.
We'll just roll it into Adam
Packer.
We'll
just
roll it
into Adam Packer.
We'll just roll
it into Adam
Packer.
We'll just
roll
it into Adam Packer.
We'll just roll it into Adam
Packer.
We'll
just
roll it into Adam Packer.
We'll just roll it into Adam
Packer.
We'll just roll it into
Adam
Packer.
We'll just roll it into Adam
We'll just roll it
into Adam
Packer.
We'll just
roll
it into
Adam
Packer.
We'll just roll it into Adam
We'll
just roll it into Adam Packer.
We'll just roll it into Adam
Packer.
Adam Packer.
We'll just roll it into Adam
Packer.
We'll just roll it into
Adam
Packer.
We'll just roll it
into Adam
Packer.
We'll just roll it into Adam
Thank you,
sir.
What is it,
sir?
What if there's drawing the tank
core I promise my wife, I
wouldn't be slugging it out in
the mud anymore?
I thought you can't see me
now.
I promise I won't be slugging
it.
I promise I
won't
be slugging it into Adam Packer.
I know
it.
There's
no
word on
it.
No one will roll it
all.
Where is it, Murray?
There's a madman out there holding
a weight flag.
That's power enough.
I only want to talk.
You're armed.
What do you want?
I've come
to
offer you and your men a
chance to walk away from this
mess.
We'll take our own chances.
Enough men have already died.
I've seen no point in further
bloodshed.
You're there 41.
It's a good
trade for the lives of your
men.
If you want to, you're going
to have to take her.
Are we done here?
I have one of your
men.
I don't know his name, but
I have something of his, if
you will allow me.
Slowly.
That doesn't prove that you're having
more than he's alive.
Perhaps,
but can you take that chance?
My men have lost a lot
of comrades and they do not
take kindly to prisoners,
but maybe if you help me,
I can help him.
Is this how all officers of
the Imperial German army conduct
themselves?
Give me the Panzer and I
promise you, you will receive the
best medical treatment lying piece of
shit.
So do we have a deal?
Well, I think we're done here.
I will stand my men down
for one hour.
After that, I take back my
offer.
You need to worry.
We're not murderers.
He's got some booze out there.
Do you think he
has
Brady?
I'm sorry, but
he's
gone.
He passes with the streets of
everything he had.
I'm already asked a lot from
you.
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready.
Are
you
ready?
I don't know who it was,
but I don't want to say
no.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I think it's safe to say
I'm looking at the finest tanker
in the entire British army.
What a day.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't
want to go
anywhere.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I
don't
want to go
anywhere.
I
don't
want to
go anywhere.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I
don't
want to go anywhere.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I
don't
want to go anywhere.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I don't want to
go anywhere.
I don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I don't want to go
anywhere.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I don't want to go
anywhere.
I
don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't
want to
go anywhere.
I
don't
want to go anywhere.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't
want
to go anywhere.
I don't want to go anywhere.